transfers.com 2016-04-07

# Privacy policy: Transfers.com

Privacy policy

This Privacy Policy is not a contract however it's giving answers to your questions about sources and kinds of information we collect, how is it used, when it may be shared with others, and how we reasonably attempt to safeguard its confidentiality and security. 

**WHAT INFORMATION WE COLLECT, HOW IS IT USED AND WHEN IT MAY BE SHARED?**

**Personal information of member**

We do not collect personally identifiable information about you unless or until you choose to make a purchase or make other services as described below. We are collecting information about you such as your name, address, phone number, e-mail address, unique login name and passwords when you register as a member. This information will be used for: personally identification; completing air, hotel, car, cruise, vacation packages, activities and other bookings; contacting you for customer service purposes, if necessary. We use your e-mail address to confirm your new member registration or to confirm each reservation on Transfers.com. Also we use your email for sending newsletter with the latest special travel deals. We will use your telephone number in the event that we need to inform you of changes or other matters that may affect your booking or trip (such as changes, cancellations, etc). Also If you complete your online profile (credit-card billing information, paper ticket delivery address, frequent-traveler or affinity numbers and other information) you can making reservations quickly without having to type in the same information again. 

**IP addresses collection**

We automatically collect your IP address, browser software information (such as Firefox, Safari, or Internet Explorer), device information, operating system. These information help us analyze your online activity (the way you are clicking through the website, how long you are staying on the website, etc). It help us to provide information that may be interesting to you.

**Third parties**

Transfers.com may share your personal information when you click on advertisement (also known as sponsored links) on Transfers.com website and authorize a third party to use your personal information for sending you additional promotional materials, providing you a product or service, etc. Sponsors may use your personal information in accordance with the sponsor's privacy practices. We will provide your personal information to the Third Party Suppliers (airline, hotel, car-rental company, cruise line or other) when you book travel. Please note that suppliers may contact you as necessary to obtain additional information about you. We encourage you to review the privacy policies of any travel supplier whose products you purchase through Transfers.com. PLEASE NOTE THAT TRANSFERS.COM DOES NOT LEASE, SELL, OR PROVIDE YOUR E-MAILS TO ANY THIRD PARTIES (EXCEPT AS MENTIONED ABOVE). 

**Cookies use**

Transfers.com is create and store cookies at your web-client to personalize your experience using the Transfers.com service. Such cookies are exclusively used for your comfort in order to save the browser settings such as log in without typing (except your password). 

**Credit card information**

Any financial transfers between you and Transfers.com are handled by third party payment services. Your payment details are disclosed to such third parties for the aim of completion of each transaction. The security and non-disclosure of such information is handled by such third parties under their current policies. Transfers.com does not sort or store numbers or any information related to your banking card. 

**Newsletters**

Transfers.com may use your e-mail (from your booking information or your member registration) for newsletters. We may send you the latest special travel deals. 

**When you book products or services on Transfers.com**

When you Book Products or Services as a Member, you must provide payment and billing information and other information. When you Book Products or Services for a third party, you must provide that third party's name and contact information, payment and billing information and other information. When you Book Products or Services as a Guest, you must provide an e-mail address so that we can send you our welcome e-mail and a confirmation of the booking. With the confirmation, we will provide you with a temporary password so that you can return to our Site if you wish to review information about your booking. 

**HOW WE PROTECT YOUR INFORMATION**

We are committed to protecting and trying to reduce the risk of loss, misuse, unauthorized access, disclosure or modification your personal information you provide to us. While no website can guarantee complete security, we have implemented appropriate administrative, technical, and physical security procedures to help protect your personal information. To protect credit card transactions while in transit, Transfers.com currently uses Secure Socket Layer technology (SSL) to encrypt Personal Data. 

**CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY**

We may update this Privacy Policy from time to time. We may notify you about material changes to this Privacy Policy by sending a notice to the email address or by placing a prominent notice on our website. Also you may regularly review the Privacy Policy on Transfers.com.
